

ABOUT ME

Hello! I'm frontend developer with experience in creating SPA using React, Redux, TypeScript. I have Knowledge in user interface, testing, and debugging processes. I am passionate about new technologies and always strive to develop in my profession. I follow the best development practices and proper application architecture.I am ready to take on new challenges and develop together with a team of professionals, creating highquality products that improve the lives of users.

SKILLS

- · React/Redux
- TypeScript/JavaScript
- · Axios/Rest API
- · HTML/CSS/SCSS
- Unit Test/Jest/TDD
- · Material-UI
- Storybook
- Figma
- Styled-components

LANGUAGE

- · English Pre-intermidiate (in progress)
- · Russian native

Anna Krasilnikova

Front-End Developer

CONTACTS

+7 964-614-58-37 akr6363@mail.ru Saint-Petersburg, Russia (ready to move)











WORK EXPERIENCE

MY PROJECT AS FRONTEND **DEVELOPER (PART-TIME)**

(2022-Present)

· Task tracker

Application build with React/Redux/TypeScript and Material UI library. Using React-hooks, Axios and Rest API. Project architectural solutions (layering UI, BLL, DAL). Performance enhancement (memo, useCallback, lazy, etc.)

Social network

Social Network SPA created with React, Redux for state management, TypeScript for scalability. Development and update components with React; RESTful (Registration/loginization/pagination etc);

Blanchard

adaptive, pixel-perfect layout for an art gallery website. HTML, CSS, JS, BEM

GEOLOGIST ENGINEER

(2020-2022)

- · Working with normative and technical documentation
- · development of a report on engineering and geological surveys in compliance with GOST and customer requirements
- · communication with the customer
- · writing scripts to automate work

EDUCATION

IT-INCUBATOR

(2023-Present)

Front-end(React, Redux, Typescript)

CHICAGA

(2023-Present)

English scholl

SKILLBOX

(2022-2023)

Web development(HTML, CSS, Java-Script)

SPBGASY,

(2016-2020)

Industrial and civil construction - bachelor